Base to Mars I got Mars water, yes sir I just
drank it, sir did I get water on Mars
and you drank it, no no sir I had brought the bottle with me, I drank it when the
remand came on ICICI Lord Oil Take Care app,
Oil Take Care app is
for buying and renewing insurance policy, but there is a
lot of things with it, nothing, nothing
sir its face can track watts, you can
also get doctor consultation, you can
also chat with experts for diet, this app
is out of the world sir tell me can this app
stop my hair fall hello hello hello
bad network sir if you get so
many features with insurance then
ICICI Lord's I Will Take Care app is
out of this world you want ICICI
Lord Oil Take Care app is out of this world